let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which flies a green, white, and orange (in that order) tricolour flag? ?",
        answer: "Italy",
        options: [
            "Ireland",
            "Spain",
            "France",
            "Italy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Where was the first example of paper money used??",
        answer: "China",
        options: [
            "Turkey",
            "Greece",
            "China",
            "Japan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Who is generally considered the inventor of the motor car?",
        answer: "Henry Ford",
        options: [
            "Henry Ford",
            "Karl Benz",
            "Nikola Tesla",
            "Charles Villa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What number was the Apollo mission that successfully put a man on the moon for the first time in human history?",
        answer: "Apollo 11",
        options: [
            "Apollo 11",
            "Apollo 12",
            "Apollo 13",
            "Apollo 14"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which of the following languages has the longest alphabet?",
        answer: "Russian",
        options: [
            "Greek",
            "Russian",
            "Arabic",
            "Egyptian"
        ]
    },
{
    numb: 6,
        question: "What is the largest US state by land mass?",
            answer: "Alaska",
                options: [
                    "Alaska",
                    "Hawaii",
                    "Texas",
                    "California"
                ]
},
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which app has the most total users?",
            answer: "Instagram",
                options: [
                    "Instagram",
                    "Facebook",
                    "Twitter",
                    "Snapchat"
                ]
},
{
    numb: 8,
    question: ") How many plays do people (generally) believe that Shakespeare wrote?",
            answer: "37",
                options: [
                    "27",
                    "37",
                    "47",
                    "57"
                ]
},
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following was considered one of the Seven Ancient Wonders??",
    answer: "Colossus of Rhodes",
                options: [
                    "Colossus of Rhodes",
                    "Great Wall of China",
                    "Colosseum",
                    "The Great Barrier Reefs"
                ]
},
{
    numb: 10,
    question: " What is the strongest muscle in the human body?",
            answer: "Jaw",
                options: [
                    "Jaw",
                    "Heart",
                    "Glutes",
                    "Biceps"
                ]
},]